Welcome to [music] this Expense Agent
video series. In this video, we talk
about brand new mobile app related to
Expense Agent.
So, what is actually new here? We
already introduced a web app for Expense
Agent, but now we want to do go one step
more. We wanted to follow employees
really where they actually work. So,
wherever you are, what you have in a
general, you have your phone by your
smartphone with you, so you can easily
capture your receipts, and that's it.
After that, AI will continue to process.
You don't need Business Central license
the same as the for web app. Everything
will be integrated automatically in the
Business Central, so system can continue
to work without any problem. And one
more thing, if you're out of internet,
now you can use offline method as well,
so you can use without any problem. And
once when you have internet, system will
synchronize without any problem
completely. So, now we want just to see
the demo. So, Claudio, please show us
demo.
>> Yeah, thank you. So, I have here the
mobile app.
This is on an Android, but of course we
do support also the iOS version. And
yeah, this is the Expense Agent mobile
app. This is the feed where you're able
to see your different expenses. This is
different from the web application,
where you know, your group your expenses
are grouped into reports and so on, but
here we're actually going for a more
kind of
new social kind of media approach, where
you just display the feeds where your
different expenses, and then if we go
into one of these expenses, let's take
the one that we're from the hotel, you
can actually see that it has different
pages, I can scroll to them, I can
actually zoom in to understand, okay,
what are the lines on it, what is the
total amount. In this case, it's $3,800.
Then of course, I can drill down into
this expense,
and then I can actually see what the
agent extracted. So, they extracted
total amount, the date of the expense,
the description, the payment means. Then
of course, the category. In in addition
to that, we also have the itemization
tab, which basically resembles all the
line items on your original expense. So,
if I drill down into one of them, then
we're going to get this nice view where
you can actually see all the details of
the specific line. In this case, it's an
overnight self-parking, the date of it,
the subcategory, quantity, and the daily
rate. And of course, you can actually
modify all of these expenses. So, that's
pretty neat, actually. I'm not going to
do anything. And now I'm going to show
you the capturing. So, for capturing,
I'm going to uh click on the plus
button, then I'm just going to click on
the scan receipt. And then we have
actually uh enabled these native
capabilities of the phone of the OS to
detect different edges, to detect
receipts. So, as as you see, as soon as
I hover on top of the receipt, then the
native capabilities are going to kick
in. Then it's going to do some, you
know, brightness with the receipt. It's
going to try, even though my receipt was
a little bit bended and so on, it's
going to try to do apply some uh yeah,
effects to it to make it easier for the
agent to read the receipt and um yeah,
and process it. So, I'm just going to
press next. And this receipt is going to
be uploaded. You can see um it was
actually quite instantaneous, the upload
process. I'm able to now read all the
details on my receipt. This is from a
ramen bar in Belgium. And then while uh
the agent now it's processing the
receipt, we can, I don't know, do
something else, for example.
Uh let's share the uh well, let's show
the share capability. So, I'm going to
go to one of my photos,
which is another receipt from a burrito
bar, and then I can actually share this
expense directly from, you know, the
native OS capabilities
with the expense agent. So, I'm just
going to share this.
And you can actually now see that the
burrito bar has been uh bar receipt has
been uploaded as well.
In addition to that,
as my colleague here mentioned, we also
do support offline mode.
So, for example, if you're coming from a
conference and while you're flying you
don't really have any internet or so and
you have some time to kill, you just
want to scan some of the expenses that
you had because we all know how
meticulous it is to do all of that
process and so on. I'm just going to I'm
going to go into airplane mode.
Okay, airplane mode on and I can
actually still scan a receipt
and I'm going to take the another
receipt from a supermarket,
scan it, send it. And now, of course,
the engine is not processing anything
because we are offline, but of course,
as soon as we go
back online,
then eventually the
app is going to connect to
Business Central and we're going to
start processing the receipt. Meanwhile,
these are all processed.
We are going to go further down. As soon
as you are done or as soon as the agent
is done processing the receipts, you can
actually go into one of these expenses.
So, let's let's take the expense from
the Ramen restaurant in Belgium and if
I'm okay with whatever the extract the
agent extracted from it, then all I need
to do to actually add it to an expense
report and submit it, I just need to tap
on the ready button.
As simple as that, it's just a seamless
experience. This is was the expense
agent app. What I showed you was an
Android phone, but of course, we also do
support iOS and we are planning to
release it to you very soon. Thank you.
>> Thank you, Claudio. So, you can expect
this new preview mode very soon as
Claudio explained and we hope you will
enjoy into new app. Thank you for
watching this video.